August 25th, Stellar Year 2148
Supplies for the Spearhead Squadron
in Combat District 1?
August 15th, Stellar Year 2148
Major, what's inside this box?
S-Special ammunition.
What's really in it?
Special ammunition.
A little more...
A little more to the right.
Stop!
Revolution Festival
Ma'am.
Want to join in the festivities, Major?
Initiate ID confirmation.
Major Vladilena Milizé.
Eastern Theater Combat District 1,
Defense Unit 1 Command and Control officer.
Activate Para-RAID.
Synchronization target:
Spearhead Processors.
Whoa!
Look at this!
If it's that hard, you should just quit.
We don't really need you for anything.
Nothing really changes
if we don't have a control officer.
Lieutenant Kukumila...
Listening to you trying to keep from losing it,
when you're not even here,
is distracting.
They don't bother you and the others?
Those... voices.
It hurts!
Mommy!
Be more careful!
Silly child.
Even without Shin, Processors have to listen
to dying screams all the time.
And dying instantly when your Juggernaut explodes
is one of the best ways to go.
We've all seen our friends get their limbs
blown off, their faces ripped to shreds,
their bodies get burned all over, or their
stomachs ripped open with guts pouring out,
screaming in pain as they died.
Compared to that,
the voices of the long dead are nothing.
Any of us could die at any time.
Good evening, everyone.
I hear you loud and clear, Major.
Sorry, it's just us guys here tonight.
Lieutenant Shuga?
Um, where's Captain Nouzen?
Did something happen in the battle today?
No, he's just sleeping. He says he's tired.
I see.
It happens sometimes.
I... We don't know the truth.
But it's probably exhausting.
Never getting a break 24 hours a day.
Because of the voices of the Legion?
It's not something that
you can do anything about.
We just get tired sometimes,
being out here, is all.
He's tired, yes,
but the stress on all of you is increasing.
With all these casualties.
Yeah.
You haven't been given one new member
since I arrived.
I'll make it happen faster.
I'll do everything I can
to make it a top priority.
Lieutenant Shuga?
Yeah, that'd be good.
This unit is defending our most important base.
It has the right to receive reinforcements first.
Until then, I'll continue to request reinforcements
from the surrounding units.
So please, hang in there a bit longer!
Yeah.
Thanks, I guess.
Of course.
August 16th, Stellar Year 2148
So you decided to overstep yourself and
complain directly to me, Major Milizé?
Sir, I can't wait any longer
for replacements for Spearhead.
I'll do anything to help them,
even beg you for aid.
I've gone to every department
for help, but...
The resupply and Processor replacement plans
for the Eastern Theater are a settled matter.
I've already informed them of your request.
You probably don't know,
as it's still an internal matter.
Really?
We're finally getting supplies?
So do your duty as best you can.
Are you ready for the
Revolution Festival party?
Attend the party in a proper dress.
Isn't that the real job of a
daughter of the Milizé family?
Understood.
August 25th, Stellar Year 2148
Lena, listen...
Why did you think
that dress was a good choice?
It's pure black, like a mourning dress.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
Thanks to this, nobody's asking me to dance.
I agree this party is stupid and boring.
But that doesn't mean looking nice
is a bad thing.
Well, I think this looks nice enough for me.
That's not the issue.
What's wrong?
One of my fiancés is over there—
the one who sent me those fancy new sweets!
See you later, Lena!
Major.
Is something wrong, Captain Nouzen?
Is it the Legion?
No, you didn't call at the usual time,
so I thought I'd check in.
Is everything okay?
If you're busy,
I can contact you another day.
I'm fine.
Sorry, this is the time
when I always call, isn't it?
What's wrong?
I wanted to let you know that
the special ammunition arrived.
It got there safely, huh?
Yes. Thank you for the fireworks.
Well, it's the Revolution Festival after all.
You saw them with your brother
and parents once, right?
I'm sure the others have similar memories.
It's a Revolution Festival tradition, huh?
Can you see the fireworks
from the  Palace Luñè where you are?
Um...
I can.
But the sky's too bright.
I'm sure the fireworks
where you're at are beautiful.
The night is dark, and the air is clean.
I wish we could see them—
Someday, let's all watch the fireworks
in District 1 together.
I'm sure you'll laugh.
I don't remember them being that bad.
Then see for yourself.
When the war's over...
When you leave the army,
we can all watch them together.
I wish Lieutenant Irma and the others
could've seen them, too.
Sorry, my timing was bad again, huh?
No, this is the first time we've ever been able
to give them a proper gun salute.
I'm sure they're pleased.
They never liked the mushy stuff.
I see.
And...
Anju was finally able to cry,
just a bit ago.
She's the type to keep things
to herself, so that meant a lot.
She won't forget Lieutenant Irma.
None of us will.
You remember my brother, right?
That made me happy.
Because I wasn't able to remember him.
Captain Nouzen...
Will you remember us as well, Major?
Of course I will.
But...
Before that, I won't let you die.
I won't let anyone else die.
August 25th, Stellar Year 2148
Hey, Eighty-Six.
This one, too.
It's a present from your master, supposedly.
As if a pig deserves a present
from a human...
How'd you manage
to get her to sign off? Beg?
We're busy with the festival, too.
Special Ammunition
What's up?
What's up, Shin?
What is this?
Fireworks?
So many...
From the Major? Wow!
Hey, Anju, um...
What is it?
I'm wondering if we can tell her.
She's sending us, like,
presents and stuff now.
Are you worried about her?
No! Why would I be worried about her?
But, um...
She wasn't scared of Shin.
So I think it'd be okay.
That's all.
Shin and Raiden, the others...
None of them are saying anything about it.
If we told her, she'd stop calling.
And that'd be better for all of us.
Yeah...
I remember what Kaie said to her...
She's not a bad person,
so she shouldn't get involved with us.
I think that's why Shin and Raiden
can't bring themselves to say it.
They think it'd hurt her.
Anju, are you okay?
With what?
You've never taken a shower
with anyone before.
I think it's okay now, honestly.
It's just the two of us.
There's no need to hide it.
Daiya... said I had pretty hair
when we first met.
He knew I was growing my hair out to hide it,
but he asked if I was growing out my hair
because it was so pretty.
Daiya's gone now.
So I think it's silly to keep worrying about it.
What about you? Don't you want to tell her?
No.
I don't think I have the right.
Even if we die,
our Reaper will take us there.
I know he'll take me there, but...
But then, what about Shin?
Who will carry his heart?
August 27th, Stellar Year 2148
Undertaker, report.
All personnel are ready to begin the attack
on the Legion forward base.
Don't forget. The base is a decoy.
Watch for the ambushers
in the surrounding area.
When we've lured them out of their holes,
two teams from the Fourth Platoon will attack.
A-Analysis complete!
Launch point is 120 kilometers east-northeast.
Estimated speed at launch is...
4000 meters per second?
It's an ultra-long range artillery cannon.
One we've never seen before!
I'm calling off the mission!
Retreat, please! Retreat!
Roger.
Seems that we shook off our pursuers.
I-I'll get you more personnel!
I'll make it happen today!
Major.
This doesn't make any sense!
The General said that they already had a plan
to bring in replacements.
Major Milizé!
Everyone, you're okay with it, right?
Yeah.
Wh-What?
Major, that's enough.
Nothing you do will change a thing.
Captain Nouzen, what are you saying?
No replacements are coming.
Not a single one. Ever.
We're going to be wiped out.
This unit is an execution ground.
Wh-What are you saying?
The "replacements" you were just talking about
are the Processors that come after us.
She means, "After we're dead."
We just got some brand-new Juggernauts.
Those are for them.
The white pigs don't intend to let a
single Eighty-Six out of the 86th District.
They conscript us with that
"five years and you're out" thing as bait.
Then they get us killed.
They really are pigs. It's terrible.
That... That's impossible!
The vast majority of Processors die
before their term is up.
It doesn't matter what you say
will happen after their term.
It's when you've got guys like us,
who manage to survive for years on a battlefield
where death is certain.
The fact that we survived means we're smart,
and the other Eighty-Six look up to us as heroes.
They can't have us leading a rebellion.
So anyone like that is sent
to the worst of the fighting,
to die there.
And those who still don't die, end up here.
Combat District 1, Unit 1, Spearhead.
The point of this place is
to make the soldiers fight until they die.
This is the last place we'll serve.
We'll all die here.
Only after the last one is dead
will replacements come.
The next group,
awaiting their own executions.
So we're not making you fight to protect us,
but just to kill you?
That's nothing but slaughter!
Did you all know...
Yes, I'm sorry.
Since when?
From the start.
Nobody who went to war,
not my sister or anybody else, came back.
And we weren't allowed out of the camps.
We all knew from the start
that white pigs don't keep their promises.
If you knew, then why did you fight?
Why not run...
or try to get revenge on the Republic?
Revenge wouldn't even be hard.
We'd just have to sit back
and let the Legion through.
We'd die, of course,
but we could take the white pigs with us.
Then why?
Until I was twelve, an old
Alba woman in District 9 looked after me.
Shin was raised by an Alba priest,
who refused to give up his land
and was sent to the camps.
Theo told you before about his captain.
Kurena knows the very worst of the Alba.
Of course, we all know how awful
the white pigs can be, but...
There are also people like Kaie,
who were abused by other Eighty-Six
because of the color of their skin.
Anju, Haruto, and Shin have white pig
or imperial blood. They're the same.
There are scum like that
among the Eighty-Six, too.
And there were a lot of proud Eighty-Six
who fought to the very end.
Even if most Alba are scum,
some of you said there wasn't
any reason to just let us die.
And not all Eighty-Six are good.
And so we all decided which we wanted to be.
Just because scum treats you like scum,
doing the same makes you no better.
If the only two paths are to die
fighting the Legion, or to die giving up,
we'll survive to the last moment
and go down fighting.
That's the reason we fight.
That's the source of our pride.
If that means protecting the white pigs,
well, that's not ideal,
but it's fine with me.
Even if you know that at the end, you'll die?
Is there anybody stupid enough to hang themselves
because they know they'll die tomorrow?
Even if you know
you're going to the gallows,
you can choose
how you're going to climb up there.
We've made our choice.
All we have to do now is survive.
Eastern Theater Combat District 16 Unit 1 "Falkes"
"Let's Go."